ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4026
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity
1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Mertopolitan Extension Division Office
/4026
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records.
3084831
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 29, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan Office. Extention Division.
3084831
- NYSSILR Questionnaire to Union Members on Why They Are or Are Not Active in Their Unions: Meatcutters Union, Male, ID# 7101-7150 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire to Union Members on Why They Are or Are Not Active in Their Unions: Meatcutters Union, Female, ID# 7201-7250 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Local 22, Female, ID# 2201-2291 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Local 22, Female, ID# 2201-2291 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Unknown Union, Male & Female (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: IUE 463, Female, ID# 4201-4269 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: IUE 463, Male, ID# 4101-4160 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: IUE 463 Shop 46, Male & Female, ID# 8001-8071 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Local 1199, Female, ID# 3201-3256 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Unknown Union, Male (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Unknown Union, Male (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notes- Consumer Counselor Training Course, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Store Workers Union, Male, ID# 5101-5178 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Store Workers Union, Male, ID# 5101-5178 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Store Workers Union, Female, ID# 5201-5314 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Store Workers Union, Female, ID# 5201-5314 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: M- Bronx Postal Union, Female, ID# 1301-1358 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Custodial Union Local 1597, Female, ID# 6301-6398 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Custodial Union Local 1597, Female, ID# 6301-6398 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Custodial Union Local 1597, Male, ID# 6101-6237 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR Questionnaire: Custodial Union Local 1597, Male, ID# 6101-6237 (Box 2, Folder 10)